# CADENCE EVA CUSTIN

330 Walnut Grove Dr | Callaway, VA 24067 | 734.252.6336 | cadence.custin@gmail.com

#### **PROFILE**

Through my career in IT, I have found teaching people how to use technology is incredibly fulfilling. I want to expand my experience as a trainer while making use of my skill in IT, creating instructional materials, and working with learning management systems.

### **EXPERIENCE**

## IT Support Analyst

Gallagher Evelius & Jones | Baltimore, MD

Mar 2020 - Mar 2023

I provided IT training to all personnel and maintained training and reference materials. I overhauled our Thomson Reuters listings and ensured everyone in the firm was signed up for and completed HIPAA training. New employees of the firm consistently thanked me for making complicated concepts digestible and understandable.

### IT Analyst

TEKsystems & Modis | Baltimore, MD

May 2017 – Mar 2020

I supported multiple companies on a contract basis, providing IT support. An integral part of my duties for these positions was training employees to use new hardware and software to help them be effective in their work.

## General Computer Labs Student Manager

James Madison University | Harrisonburg, VA

May 2008 – May 2012

I trained and scheduled lab assistants and supervised all aspects of day-to-day computer lab maintenance. To improve processes, I overhauled existing reference documentation, updating information and adding significantly to it.

## **KEY SKILLS & CHARACTERISTICS**

Learning Management Systems • MS Office Suite

Empathetic, patient instruction • Explaining complicated concepts

Eagle Scout

## **EDUCATION**

# Juris Doctorate

Michigan State University College of Law

May 2015

#### **Bachelor of Music**

James Madison University

May 2012